{
    "subject": "resource/Pazuzu_(The_Exorcist)",
    "predicate": "ontology/portrayer",
    "object": "resource/Rupert_Degas",
    "human_readable": "Pazuzu was portrayed by Rupert Egas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9856038093566895,
            "question": "Is Rupert Egas known for playing Pazuzu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9847453236579895,
            "question": "In what film or production was Pazuzu portrayed by Rupert Egas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8551919460296631,
            "question": "Who portrayed Pazuzu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.802459180355072,
            "question": "What character did Rupert Egas play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6711945533752441,
            "question": "What kind of character is Pazuzu typically portrayed as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6319496035575867,
            "question": "Are there other actors who have played Pazuzu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37080299854278564,
            "question": "What is Pazuzu often depicted as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33608758449554443,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Rupert Egas's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29365360736846924,
            "question": "What are some notable characteristics associated with Pazuzu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18287737667560577,
            "question": "What is the significance of Pazuzu in mythology or folklore?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pazuzu was portrayed by Rupert Egas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8687_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable characteristics associated with Pazuzu?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8687_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about Rupert Egas's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8687_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Pazuzu often depicted as?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8687_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8687_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention various people who have voiced or portrayed Pazuzu, such as Eileen Dietz, Mercedes McCambridge, and Rupert Degas, but there is no mention of someone named Rupert Egas being associated with the character."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention anyone named Rupert Egas portraying Pazuzu. The information given mentions that Pazuzu's face was portrayed by Eileen Dietz, and voices of various actors have played the character in different films and series. There is no reference to a character named Rupert Egas."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Rupert Degas portrayed Pazuzu in \"Exorcist: The Beginning\" and not Eileen Dietz.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The correct voice portrayal of Pazuzu in Exorcist: The Beginning was actually David Hewlett, not Rupert Degas.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided states that Pazuzu's face was portrayed by Eileen Dietz, not Rupert Egas.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}